export default data = [
  {
      question: "John’s clock is not functioning _____. The alarm rings even when it’s not set to go off.",
      options: ["tenderly","properly","solidly","favorably"],
      correct_option: "properly"
  },
  {
      question: "Michael has decided to _____ a career in physics and has set his mind on becoming a professor.",
      options: ["pursue","swear","reserve","draft"],
      correct_option: "pursue"
  },
  {
      question: "Peter plans to hike in a _____ part of Africa, where he might not meet another human being for days.",
      options: ["native","tricky","remote","vacant"],
      correct_option: "remote"
  },
  {
      question: "People in this community tend to _____ with the group they belong to, and often put group interests before personal ones.",
      options: ["appoint","eliminate","occupy","identify"],
      correct_option: "identify"
  },
  {
      question: "I mistook the man for a well-known actor and asked for his autograph; it was really _____.",
      options: ["relaxing","embarrassing","appealing","defending"],
      correct_option: "embarrassing"
  },
  {
      question: "After spending most of her salary on rent and food, Amelia _____ had any money left for entertainment and other expenses.",
      options: ["barely","fairly","merely","readily"],
      correct_option: "barely"
  },
  {
      question: "In the Bermuda Triangle, a region in the western part of the North Atlantic Ocean, some airplanes and ships were reported to have mysteriously disappeared without a _____.",
      options: ["guide","trace","code","print"],
      correct_option: "trace"
  },
  {
      question: "Shouting greetings and waving a big sign, Tony _____ the passing shoppers to visit his shop and buy the freshly baked bread.",
      options: ["accessed","edited","imposed","urged"],
      correct_option: "urged"
  },
  {
      question: "With a continuous 3 km stretch of golden sand, the beach attracts artists around the world each summer to create amazing _____ with its fine soft sand.",
      options: ["constitutions","objections","sculptures","adventures"],
      correct_option: "sculptures"
  },
  {
      question: "The clouds parted and a _____ of light fell on the church, through the windows, and onto the floor.",
      options: ["dip","beam","spark","path"],
      correct_option: "beam"
  },
  {
      question: "Instead of a gift, Tim’s grandmother always _____ some money in the birthday card she gave him.",
      options: ["enclosed","installed","preserved","rewarded"],
      correct_option: "enclosed"
  },
  {
      question: "While winning a gold _____ is what every Olympic athlete dreams of, it becomes meaningless if it is achieved by cheating.",
      options: ["signal","glory","medal","profit"],
      correct_option: "medal"
  },
  {
      question: "The thief went into the apartment building and stole some jewelry. He then _____ himself as a security guard and walked out the front gate.",
      options: ["balanced","calculated","disguised","registered"],
      correct_option: "disguised"
  },
  {
      question: "Due to numerous accidents that occurred while people were playing Pokémon GO, players were advised to be _____ of possible dangers in the environment.",
      options: ["aware","ashamed","doubtful","guilty"],
      correct_option: "aware"
  },
  {
      question: "Sherlock Holmes, a detective in a popular fiction series, has impressed readers with his amazing powers of _____ and his knowledge of trivial facts.",
      options: ["innocence","estimation","assurance","observation"],
      correct_option: "observation"
  },
]
